Movie Poster and Associated Materials Collection, 1908-1977
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 3: Oversize Movie Posters, 1937-1967
  - Arena, style B, 1953; 6 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Arena, 1953; 6 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Cyclone, 1941; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Raiders, 1965; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - The Arizonian, style A, 1951; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - The Baron of Arizona, 1950; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Cattle Empire, 1958; 2 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Chicken Every Sunday, 1949; 2 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Coogan’s Bluff, 1968; 2 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Deadly Companions, style A, 1961; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Deadly Companions, style B, 1961; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Deadly Companions, 1961; 6 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Devil’s Canyon, 1953; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Distant Trumpet, 1964; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Firecreek (Les 5 Hos La Loi), France, 1968; 2 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Geronimo, 1962; 2 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Geronimo, 1962; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Grand Canyon, 1949; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Hombre, France, 1967; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Lilies of the Field, 1964; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - One Foot in Hell, 1960; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - The Plainsman, 1966; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - The Purple Hills, 1961; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - The Purple Hills, 1961; 6 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Rider from Tucson, 1950; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - The Rounders, 1965; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Shadows of Tombstone, 1953; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - The Silencers (Matt Helm, Agent Tres Special), Belgium, 1966; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Stars over Arizona, 1937; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - A Thunder of Drums, 1961; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - A Time for Killing, 1967; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Tucson, 1948; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Walk the Proud Land, 1956; 3 sheet (Drawer oversize 2, Folder 1)
- Series 4: Press Books / Press Kits, 1936-1976
  This series contains promotion press books and press kits. The press books are typically 8 ½" x 11" and are approximately 20 to 30 pages stapled. Press books typically contain the film's full cast listing, major star biographies, a complete story line, and full credit information. Press kits typically come in a standard sized folder and contain a press book as well as various promotional materials. This series is arranged alphabetically by film title. Posters with a foreign title are listed under the American title when determined.
  - 40 Guns to Apache Pass (Gewehre Zum Apachen Pass), German, 1967 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - 100 Rifles, Spain, 1969 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Andy Warhol's Lonesome Cowboys, 1968 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Animals, 1978 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Apache Chief, 1948 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Apache Rifles (Austand in Arizona), German, 1965 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Apache Rifles, 1965 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Colt Returns (Arizona Vuelve), Italy, 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Days, 1936 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Raiders (Goldtransport durch Arizona), German, 1965 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Roundup, 1942 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Badlanders (Arizona Prison Federal), Spain, 1958 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Barquero (Los Forajidos de Rio Bravo), Italy, 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Barquero (Los Forajidos de Rio Bravo), Spain, 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Barquero (Los Forajidos de Rio Bravo),(2 copies), 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Billy Jack, 1973 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Blood on the Arrow,(2 copies), 1964 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Branded (Marcado a Fuego), Spain, 1950 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Cancel My Reservation, 1972 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Cancel My Reservation, 1972 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Day of Anger, 1969 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - A Distant Trumpet, 1964 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Fort Yuma, 1955 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Gunfight at the O.K. Corral (Duelo de Titantes), 1957 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Gunfight at the O.K. Corral, 1957 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Gunsmoke in Tucson, 1958 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Hail Hero! (Hail Heroe!), Spain, 1971 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Heaven with a Gun, 1969 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Hombre (Man Nannte Ihn Hombre), German, 1967 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Hour of the Gun (La Hora de las Pistolas), Spain, 1967 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - How the West Was Won (La Conquista del Oeste), Spain, 1964 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - I Killed Geronimo, 1950 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Jesus Trip, 1971 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Kid Morelo, 1965 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Land Raiders (Al Inferno, Gringo!), Spain, 1969 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Land Raiders,(3 copies), 1969 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Last Challenge, 1967 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Last Hard Men, 1976 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Little Fauss and Big Halsy (El Precio del Fracaso), Spain, 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Little Fauss and Big Halsy, 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - MacKenna's Gold (El Oro de MacKenna), Spain, 1969 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - MacKenna's Gold, 1969 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Magnificent 7 Ride (El Desafio de los 7 Magnificos), 1972 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Magnificent 7 Ride, 1972 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Man and Boy, 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Man of the West, 1958 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Naked Angels / Pit Stop, 1969 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Name of the Game is Kill, 1968 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - One Foot in Hell, 1960 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Rage, 1972 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Rebels from Arizona (Los Rebeldes de Arizona), Spain, 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Red Sun, 1972 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Rounders, 1965 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Santa Fe Trail, 1940 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Savage Guns, 1962 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Silencers, Belgium, 1966 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Squad Car, 1960 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Stage to Mesa City, 1947 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Sugarfoot (Ein Fremder Kam Nach Arizona), German,(2 copies), 1951 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Sugarfoot, 1951 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Stalking Moon, 1968 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Suppose They Gave a War and Nobody Came, 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - The Tall T (Um Kopf und Kragen), German, 1957 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Ten Wanted Men (Racher in Schwarz), German, 1955 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - There Was a Crooked Man…, 1970 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - A Thunder of Drums (Fort Comanche), Spain, 1961 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - A Thunder of Drums, 1961 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Ulzana's Raid,(3 copies), 1972 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Valdez is Coming (Que Viene Valdez!), Spain, 1971 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Walk the Proud Land (Ritt in den Tod), German, 1956 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Wild Horse Mesa, 1947 (Drawer 8, Folder 1)
- Series 5: Lobby Cards, 1928-1973
  This series contains lobby cards (11" x 14") which typically come in sets that give a pictorial synopsis of a film's plot. This series is arranged alphabetically by film title. Posters with a foreign title are listed under the American title when determined.
  - 8 on the Lam, 1967; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - 40 Guns to Apache Pass, 1967; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Alias Billy the Kid, 1946; 2 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Animals, 1971; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Apache Country, 1952; 2 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Apache Drums, 1951; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Apache Gold, 1965; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Apache Rifles, 1965; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Apache Territory, 1958; 7 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Apache Uprising, 1965; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Apache War Smoke, 1952; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Apache Woman, 1955; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Arena, 1953; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Arizona, 1940; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Bushwackers, 1967; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Arizona Cowboy, 1950; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Manhunt, 1951; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Raiders, 1965; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Arizona Ranger, 1948; 2 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Territory, 1950; 9 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Arizonian (re-release), 1951; 13 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Ballad of Cable Hogue, 1970; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Battle at Apache Pass, 1952; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Beyond the Purple Hills, 1950; 3 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Billy Jack, 1973; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Black Eagle, 1948; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Brighty of the Grand Canyon, 1967; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Cancel My Reservation, 1972; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Canyon City, 1943; 7 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Canyon Raiders, 1951; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Canyon River, 1956; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Carson City Raiders, 1948; 3 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Challenge of the Range, 1949; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Cheyenne Autumn, 1964; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Conquest of the West (La Conquesta del Oeste), Spain, undated; 10 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Cowboy and the Indians, 1949; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Cyclone Prairie Rangers, 1944; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Day of Anger, 1969; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Deadly Companions, 1961; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Death Valley Manhunt, 1943; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Desert Horseman, 1946; 7 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Desperados of Dodge City, 1948; 7 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Devil's Canyon, 1953; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Doc, 1971; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Firebrands of Arizona, 1944; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Fort Bowie, 1957; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Galloping Thunder, 1946; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Gauchos of El Dorado, 1941; 3 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Gay Ranchero, 1948; 4 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Geronimo (re-release), 1949; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Grand Canyon, 1948; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Grand Canyon Trail, 1948; 2 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Gunfight at the O.K. Corral (Duelo de Titanes), Spain, 1957; 12 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Gunfight at the O.K. Corral, 1957; 8 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Gunning for Vengeance, 1946; 2 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Gunplay, 1951; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Hawk of Wild River, 1952; 6 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Hellfire, 1949; 6 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Hombre, France, 1967; 18 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Horsemen of the Plains, 1928; 2 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Hour of the Gun (Die Funf Geachteten), German, 1967; 22 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Indian Agent, 1948; 7 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Law of the Golden West, 1949; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Lilies of the Field, 1963; 7 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - MacKenna's Gold (El Oro de MacKenna), Spain, 1969; 12 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - MacKenna's Gold (El Oro de MacKenna), Spain, 1969; 12 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Marshal of Cripple Creek, 1947; 1 item (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Mule Train, 1950; 3 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Mule Train, 1950; 3 items (Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - The Old Frontier, 1950; 8 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Outcasts of the Trail, 1949; 4 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - The Phantom Stagecoach, 1957; 3 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Quick on the Trigger, 1948; 1 item (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Renegades of the Sage, 1947; 7 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Rider from Tucson, 1950; 8 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Riders in the Sky, 1949; 1 item (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Ridin' on a Rainbow, 1941; 2 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Ridin' the Outlaw Trail, 1950; 6 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Robin Hood of the Pecos, 1941; 3 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - The Rough, Tough West, 1952; 8 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Shadows of Tombstone, 1953; 8 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Sheriff of Tombstone, 1941; 5 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Smoky Canyon, 1951; 4 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Song of Arizona, 1946; 2 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Stage to Tucson, 1950; 8 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Stagecoach Kid, 1949; 6 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Star in the Dust, 1956; 4 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - The Storm Rider, 1957; 2 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Sundown Valley, 1944; 3 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - A Time for Killing (La Poursuite des Tuniques Bleues), France, 1967; 10 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Toughest Gun in Tombstone, 1958; 1 item (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Toughest Man in Arizona, 1952; 8 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Trail of Robin Hood, 1950; 3 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Trail of the Rustlers, 1950; 7 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Trail Street, 1947; 7 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Trigger, Jr., 1950; 4 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Tucson, 1948; 8 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Under Fiesta Stars, 1941; 2 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Utah Wagon Train, 1951; 1 item (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Wagon Wheels Westward, 1945; 1 item (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - War Drums, 1945; 8 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - West of Sonora, 1948; 8 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Whirlwind Raiders, 1948; 6 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Wildfire, 1945; 5 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Wild Horse Canyon, 1938; 3 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Young Bill Hickok, 1940; 2 items (Drawer 10, Folder 1)
- Series 6: Still Photographs, 1950 – 1977
  This series is arranged alphabetically by film title and contains both color and black and white promotional stills.
  - Apache Uprising, 1965; 11 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Raiders, 1965; 8 color stills (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Blood on the Arrow, 1964; 8 color stills (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Blood on the Arrow, 1964; 8 color stills (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cry for Me Billy, 1977; 8 color stills (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A Distant Trumpet, 1964; 8 color stills (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Five Guns to Tombstone, 1961; 15 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Fort Yuma, 1955; 8 color stills (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gunsmoke in Tucson, 1958; 36 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hombre, 1967; 6 black and white stills, 2 color stills (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Man and Boy, 1971; 3 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Murphy's Romance, 1985; 6 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Santiago, 1956; 2 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Southwest Passage, 1954; 2 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Stalking Moon, 1969; 8 color stills (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Stay Away, Joe, 1968; 1 black and white still (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sugarfoot, 1951; 2 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Suppose They Gave a War and Nobody Came, 1970; 1 black and white still (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - There was a Crooked Man, 1970; 1 black and white still (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 3:10 to Yuma, 1957; 5 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - A Thunder of Drums, 1961; 12 color stills (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Thunder over Arizona, 1956; 8 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Toughest Man in Arizona, 1952; 8 color stills (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Walk the Proud Land, 1956; 5 black and white photographs (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Winchester '73, 1950; 9 black and white photographs (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Zabriskie Point, 1970; 3 black and white stills (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Series 7: Miniature Posters, undated
  This series contains miniature posters which range in size. These posters typically duplicate the image of a film's one sheet and were commonly printed as advances to generate interest in a film and were usually given away at premiers or special screenings. This series is arranged alphabetically by film title. Posters with a foreign title are listed under the American title when determined.
  - 100 Rifles, Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Arizona Colt Returns (Arizona Vuelve), undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Arizona Raiders (El Renegado Arizona), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bad Man of Brimstone (El Tigre de Arizona), undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Blood on the Arrow (Flechas Sangrientas), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Branded (Marcado a Fuego), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Doc (Duelo a Muerte en O.K. Corral), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Escape from Fort Bravo (Flugten fra Fort Bravo), Danish, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Five Thousand Dollars on One Ace (Los Pistoleros de Arizona), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Frontier Hellcats, (Los Buitres), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Gal Who Took the West (To Cowboys Een Pige), Danish, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Geronimo, Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Geronimo (Venganza India), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Gunfight at the O.K. Corral (Duel de Titantes), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Guns of the Magnificent Seven (El Desafio de los 7 Magnificos), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Hombre (Un Hombre), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Hombre, Danish, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - How the West Was Won (La Conquista del Oeste), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Last Wagon (Praerievognen), Danish, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Lilies of the Field (Los Lirios del Valle), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - MacKenna's Gold (El Oro de MacKenna), undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - My Darling Clementine, Danish, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Plainsmen (El Nations Helte), Danish, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Stalking Moon (La Noche de los Gigantes), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - There Was a Crooked Man…(El Dia de Los Tramposos), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - A Thunder of Drums (Fort Comanche), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - A Time for Killing (La Cabalgada de los Malditos), Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Series 8: Scripts, 1938, 1950
  This series is arranged alphabetically by film title and contains final and 2nd drafts of film scripts.
  - Salomy Jane, Final Draft, by Frances Hyland and Albert Ray, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Stage to Tucson, 2nd Draft, by Bob Williams, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 27)